Guide to the Gerhard Casper, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0672
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- President's records, 1995-1996; Accession ARCH-1998-129
  - shc & ucsf merger, see shs 15 next, 11/95 - 8/96; SHS 3ucsf (Box 16)
  - Hospital-special- Sandra Jensen file, October '95; SHS 3 (Box 17)
  - SHS Administration, 9/95 - 8/96; SHS 3 (Box 17)
  - Hospital Board of Directors, 9/95 - 8/96; SHS 4 (Box 17)
  - Lucille Salter Packard Child. Hosp., 10/12/95 - 8/29/96; SHS 7 (Box 17)
  - Howard Hughes Medical Institute, 96 an. rpt - 4/25/96; SHS 9 (Box 17)
  - Beckman Center, Dept of Biochem, 6/95 - 2/96; SHS 10 (Box 17)
  - Affiliated Hosp's/Clinics, Etc., 9/21/95 - 6/8/96; SHS 13 (Box 17)
  - Patient Relations, 9/95 - 8/6/96; SHS 14 (Box 17)
  - Organizations, Misc and Ad Hoc, 9/95 - 8/96; O 1 (Box 17)
  - Council on Competitiveness, 9/27/95 - 6/96; O 1.2 (Box 17)
  - Stanford Research Institute, 9/20/95 - 3/14/96; O 2.11 (Box 17)
  - Education Groups (Outside, Misc), 9/95 - 8/96; O 3 (Box 17)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Ed, 9/15/95 - 7/23/96; O 3.1 (Box 17)
  - CA Academy of Science, 9/13/95 - 8/96; O 3.2 (Box 17)
  - Consortium of Social Science Assoc., 4/4/94 only; O 3.3 (Box 18)
  - American Academy of Arts/Sciences, 9/18/95 - 8/23/96; O 3.7 (Box 18)
  - American Council on Education, 9/19/95 - 7/24/96; O 3.8 (Box 18)
  - CA Bus/Higher Education Forum, 5/10/96 & 9/23/96 only; O 3.8.1 (Box 18)
  - Nat'l Assoc. of Indep Coll & Univ's, 12/29/95 - 3/29/96; O 3.10 (Box 18)
  - Amer. Council of Learned Societies, 2/26/96 & 8/17/96 only; O 3.12 (Box 18)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 9/95 - 8/96; O 3.25 (Box 18)
  - Aspen Institute, 11/20/95 - 5/23/96; O 3.37 (Box 18)
  - Institute of International Education, 6/18/96 & 6/21/96 only; O 3.38 (Box 18)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 10/95 - 8/6/96; O 3.43 (Box 18)
  - Nat'l Academy of Engineers, 10/18/95 chron only; O 3.43.1 (Box 18)
  - NCAA Nat'l Colleg. Ath. Assoc., 9/13/95 -8/9/96; O 3.44 (Box 18)
  - Pac 10, 8/22/95 - 6/2/96; O 3.47 (Box 18)
  - Western Interstate Comm for Hi. Ed., 8/10/95 - 6/21/96; O 3.51 (Box 19)
  - CA Bus. & Higher Ed. Forum, 7/18/95 - 8/8/96; O 3.56 (Box 19)
  - Amer. Assoc. Higher Ed, 9/8/95 - 11/13/95; O 3.57 (Box 19)
  - Athletic Organizations Misc, 5/15/95 - 6/24/96; O 4 (Box 19)
  - Medical Org's Misc., 10/13/95 -8/16/96; O 5 (Box 19)
  - Political Groups Misc, 3/2/94 -4/22/96; O 6 (Box 19)
  - Research Org's Misc, 9/9/95 - 7/1/96; O 7 (Box 19)
  - Amer. Assoc. Advancement/Science, 2/4/94 - 11/22/95; O 7.2 (Box 19)
  - Rand Inst. for Civil Justice, 2/19/96 & 3/26/96 only; O 7.9 (Box 19)
  - National Research Council, 8/26/1996 only; O 7.11 (Box 19)
  - Council of Pres. Univ. Res. Assoc., 11/20/95 - 1/3/96; O 7.16 (Box 19)
  - Other coll/universities misc, 2/24/95 - 8/9/96; O 8 (Box 19)
  - Assoc. of Amer. Colleges/univ's, 2/5/96 and 11/19/96 only; O 8.6 (Box 19)
  - Assoc. of Amer. Universities, 9/95 - 8/96; O 8.7 (Box 19)
  - Assoc of Governing Boards univ/coll's, 2/29/96 & 5/21/96 only; O 8.8 (Box 19)
  - Assoc of Independent CA Coll/univ's, 12/7/95 - 8/19/96; O 8.9 (Box 19)
  - Assoc. of Amer. Law Schools, 11/30/95 only; O 8.10 (Box 19)
  - CA State Universities, 9/12/95 - 7/16/96; O 8.17 (Box 19)
  - Columbia University, 1/24/96-4/12/96; O 8.18 (Box 19)
  - Cornell University, 1/5/96-5/28/96; O 8.19 (Box 19)
  - Harvard University, O 8.23 (Box 20)
  - Princeton Univ/Accreditation 1994, Accredit.'94, &'95/'96 stuff; O 8.36 (Box 20)
  - Nine Provosts, 9/8/93-4/5/96; O 8.39 (Box 20)
  - Univ of CA - all campuses, 9/15/95-8/16/96; O 8.43 (Box 20)
  - University of Chicago, 11/10/95-8/20/96; O 8.44 (Box 20)
  - University of Michigan, 9/29/95-6/20/96; O 8.45 (Box 20)
  - University of Oregon, 3/17/95-8/30/96; O 8.47 (Box 20)
  - University of Southern CA, 10/11/95-5/23/96; O 8.49 (Box 20)
  - WASC West. Assoc Sch's/Colleges President's Comm on accredit., O 8.52 (Box 20)
  - WASC West. Assoc Sch's/Colleges, & regular 11/10/95-8/15/96; O 8.52 (Box 20)
  - Yale University, 9/19/95-8/5/96; O 8.53 (Box 20)
  - Western College Association, 12/6/95 - 3/12/96; O 8.54 (Box 20)
  - Inaugurationa Other Schools, 9/95-8/23/96; O 8.55 (Box 20)
  - Bay Area Economic Forum, 2/29/96 - 8/22/96; O 11 (Box 20)
  - CA Council on Science and Tech, 8/95 - 4/96; O 12 (Box 21)
  - GAAC German Amer Acad. Council, 7/95 - 3/14/96; O 14 (Box 21)
  - American Philosophical Society, 4/26/96 - 8/15/96; O 15 (Box 21)
  - Research Misc, 9/9/95-8/19/96; R 0 (Box 21)
  - Sponsored Projects, 8/31/94-3/4/96; R 1 (Box 21)
  - Stanford Center for Chicano Research, 3/12/96 only; R 1.3 (Box 21)
  - Inst. for Res. on Women and Gender, 10/26/95 only; R 1.8 (Box 21)
  - Institute for International Studies, 4/25/95-8/96; R 1.12 (Box 21)
  - Research Policies, 1/31/96-5/2/96; R 2 (Box 21)
  - Inst. for Support for Resch. Misc., 3/26/96 only; R 3 (Box 21)
  - Research Proposals Misc., 7/29/96 & 8/3/96 only; R 4 (Box 21)
  - Inst. for Review Bd. for Human Sub's, 9/29/95-10/26/95; R 5 (Box 21)
  - Stanford Leadership Institute, 12/29/95-6/12/96; R 7 (Box 21)
  - The Science Coalition, 1/9/96-7/96; R 8 (Box 21)
  - Kurt Schwehr student grievance file, 2/95 - 2/96; ST 1 (Box 21)
  - Students Misc, 9/95 - 8/20/96; ST 1 (Box 21)
  - Student Groups Misc, 10/18/95 - 8/16/96; ST 1.1 (Box 21)
  - ASSU Assoc, Students of SU, 10/18/95 - 8/12/96; ST 2 (Box 21)
  - ASSU Senate, 11/3 & 7/95 only; ST 2.10 (Box 21)
  - Stanford Band, 9/7/95 - 5/28/96; ST 3.4 (Box 21)
  - Bechtel International Center, 12/20/95 - 8/26/96; ST 3.5 (Box 21)
  - Hillel, Bnai Birith, 11/4/95 - 6/18/96; ST 3.7 (Box 21)
  - KZSU Student Radio, 10/24/95 - 11/2/95; ST 3.18 (Box 21)
  - Stanford Daily, 11/9/95 - 11/22/95; ST 3.23.7 (Box 21)
  - Stanford Review, 10/9/95 - 12/28/95; ST 3.23.8 (Box 21)
  - Haas Public Service Center, 3/1/95 - 8/19/96; ST 3.29 (Box 21)
  - John Gardner Fellowship, 10/5/95 - 5/4/96; ST 3.29/1 (Box 21)
  - Campus Compact, 7/5/95 - 8/26/95; ST 3.35 (Box 21)
  - Student Deaths, (2) 9/6/95 chrons only; ST 5.2 (Box 21)
  - Freshmen, 9/26 & 10/3/95 only; ST 5.3 (Box 21)
  - Scholarships, 11/6/95 - 6/14/96; ST 7 (Box 21)
  - Asian Pacific Scholarship Program, 10/11/95 - 6/12/96; ST 7.1 (Box 21)
  - Student/Parent Correspondences, 9/95-7/15/96; ST 8 (Box 21)
  - Jean Fetter chrons 12/95-12/96 (Box 22)
  - Big Game Brunch 1995 (Box 22)
  - Brad Efron Summer Party 8/4/94 (Box 22)
  - Leah Kaplan lunch6/10/96 (Box 22)
  - Susan Sontag Dinner 4/11/96 (Box 22)
- President's records, 1996-1997; Accession ARCH-1999-171
  - Provost's Office, 12/31/96 - 7/8/97; AA 1 (Box 1)
  - Dean of the Chapel, R. Gregg (Academic), 12/3/96 - 8/1/97; AA 1.8 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Graduate Fellowships, 10/25/96 - 8/12/97; AA 1.12 (Box 1)
  - Graduate Students /Studies, Issues, 1/30/96 - 7/7/97; AA 1.13 (Box 1)
  - Emeriti, 11/12/96 - 7/8/97; AA 2.2 (Box 1)
  - Affirmative Action, Faculty/Staff, 10/17/96 - 8/22/97; AA 2.3.3 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Develop. (Faculty Affairs, misc), 9/24/96 - 7/25/97; AA 2.7 (Box 1)
  - University Fellows, 1/6/97 - 7/2/97; AA 2.9 (Box 1)
  - Teaching Assistants/Research Associates, 1/27/97 & 1/29/97; AA 2.11 (Box 1)
  - Undergraduate Issues, 9/9/96 - 8/21/97; AA 3 (Box 1)
  - Accreditation Issues -very general, 11/25/96 & 1/15/97; AA 3.4 (Box 1)
  - Ratings/Rankings - US News & World Report, special: 9/19/94 - 8/27/97; AA 3.5 (Box 1)
  - Cultures, Ideas, Values (CIV), 9/26/96 - 8/15/97; AA 3.5.1 (Box 1)
  - Continuing Studies, 10/11/96 - 4/16/97; AA 3.6 (Box 1)
  - Television, Cable, CH 51, etc, 12/2/96 - 8/13/97; AA 3.9.1 (Box 1)
  - Sophomore Affairs/Soph College, 9/16/96 - 8/28/97; AA 3.18.2 (Box 1)
  - School of Humanities and Sciences, 9/17/96 - 8/28/97; AA 4.1 (Box 1)
  - Humanities Center, 10/21/96 - 8/1/97; AA 4.1.1/2 (Box 1)
  - Anthropology Department, 1/29/97 & 2/17/97; AA 4.1.5 (Box 1)
  - Applied Physics, Dept of, 2/12/97 - 5/19/97; AA 4.1.8 (Box 1)
  - Art, Dept of (Academic), 34073; AA 4.1.9 (Box 1)
  - Chemistry, Dept of, 10/29/96 - 6/14/97; AA 4.1.13 (Box 1)
  - Classics Department, 12/5/96 - 2/20/97; AA 4.1.14 (Box 1)
  - Communication, Dept of, 33892; AA 4.1.15 (Box 1)
  - Computer Science, Dept of (Sch.Engr.), 11/20/96 - 2/28/97; AA 4.1.17 (Box 1)
  - Drama, Dept of, 10/16/96 - 7/31/97; AA 4.1.18 (Box 1)
  - Economics, Dept of, 10/4/96 - 5/19/97; AA 4.1.20 (Box 2)
  - Stanford Institute for Economic Policy Research SIEPR, 9/27/96 - 8/19/97; AA 4.1.20/1 (Box 2)
  - English, Dept of, 10/4/96 - 6/26/97; AA 4.1.21 (Box 2)
  - French & Italian, Dept of, 9/26/96 - 8/9/97; AA 4.1.22 (Box 2)
  - German, Dept of at SU, 11/6/96 - 8/18/97; AA 4.1.24 (Box 2)
  - History, Dept of, 9/30/96 - 5/28/97; AA 4.1.25 (Box 2)
  - Human Biology Program, 33974; AA 4.1.26 (Box 2)
  - Mathematics Dept., 10/8/96 - 2/12/97; AA 4.1.27 (Box 2)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (HMS), 9/23/96 - 7/18/97; AA 4.1.28 (Box 2)
  - Music, Dept of, 9/19/96 - 8/29/97; AA 4.1.29 (Box 2)
  - Athletics, 9/10/96 - 8/28/97; AA 4.1.30 (Box 2)
  - Football Games, Tyrone Willingham, Rose Bowl. etc, 9/1/96 - 8/25/97 (gaieties ); AA 4.1.30/1 (Box 2)
  - Philosophy, Dept of, 1/10/97 - 7/1/97; AA 4.1.32 (Box 2)
  - Physics, Dept of, 10/4/96 - 6/2/97; AA 4.1.33 (Box 2)
  - Political Science Dept, 9/3/96 - 8/22/97; AA 4.1.34 (Box 2)
  - Psychology, Dept of (not medical), 10/14/96 - 3/17/97; AA 4.1.35 (Box 2)
  - Slavic Languages & Literature, 33903; AA 4.1.38 (Box 2)
  - Statistics Department, 9/20/96 & 10/23/96; AA 4.1.42 (Box 2)
  - Center for Research on Econ. Dev & Policy, 10/1/96 - 8/28/97; AA 4.1.48 (Box 2)
  - Graduate School of Business, 9/27/96 - 8/25/97; AA 4.2 (Box 2)
  - Earth Sciences, School of, 10/8/96 - 8/19/97; AA 4.3 (Box 2)
  - Engineering, School of, 9/4/96 - 8/29/97; AA 4.4 (Box 2)
  - Electrical Engineering Department, 10/8/96 - 2/28/97; AA 4.4.5 (Box 2)
  - Civil Engineering, 33866; AA 4.4.12 (Box 2)
  - Education, School of, 9/25/96 - 8/5/97; AA 4.5 (Box 2)
  - Hoover Institution General, 9/96 - 8/97; AA 4.9 (Box 3)
  - Center for Innovation in Education, 12/7/96 - 5/16/97; AA 4.10.5 (Box 3)
  - Cent for Intl Security/Cooperation, 10/4/96 - 8/12/97; AA 4.10.6 (Box 3)
  - Center for Latin American Studies, 11/25/96 - 8/20/97; AA 4.11 (Box 3)
  - Russian/East Euro Studies Center, 2/4 & 2/14/97; AA 4.11.1 (Box 3)
  - Libraries @ SU - general catch-all, 9/19/96 - 7/23/97; AA 4.12 (Box 3)
  - Cent for the Study of Lang/Infor CSLI, 34030; AA 4.14.1 (Box 3)
  - Law School, 9/10/96 - 8/22/97; AA 4.15 (Box 3)
  - Infor Tech Services ITSS, 9/13/96 - 8/14/97; AA 4.22 (Box 3)
  - Awards & Prizes, general and misc, 9/24/96 - 8/21/97; AA 5 (Box 3)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 10/8/96 - 7/7/97; AA 5.2 (Box 4)
  - Presidcent's Scholars, 11/11/96 - 9/5/97; AA 5.3 (Box 4)
  - Gold Spike Award, 3/5/97 - 4/29/97; AA 5.26 (Box 4)
  - Grants Misc, 5/19/97 - 8/12/97; AA 6 (Box 4)
  - Scholarships Misc., 2/24/97 - 4/16/97; AA 7 (Box 4)
  - Fellowships, Misc/General Infor., 8/16/96 - 8/15/97; AA 8 (Box 4)
  - Fullbright Fellowships/Scholarships, 11/22/96 - 8/15/97; AA 8.16 (Box 4)
  - Guggenheim Memorial Fellowship, 12/30/96 - 4/10/97; AA 8.17 (Box 4)
  - Knight Fellowships/Foundation, Sept '96 - July '97; AA 8.25 (Box 4)
  - Terman Fellows, 9/96 - 10/4/96; AA 8.30 (Box 4)
  - Harry Camp Memorial Lectures, 1/23/97 - 3/14/97; AA 9.7 (Box 4)
  - Tanner Lectures, 12/5/96 - 7/22/97; AA 9.19 (Box 4)
  - Faculty, Profs, Chairs, Visiting Profs, 9/27/96 - 7/31/97; AA 10 (Box 4)
  - Stanford Miscellaneous, 12/13/96 - 8/28/97; AD 1 (Box 4)
  - Disability Resources, 33904; AD 2.11 (Box 4)
  - Alcoholism/Drugs, 11/96 - 1/15/97; AD 2.15/1 (Box 4)
  - ROTC, 11/9/96 - 5/5/97; AD 2.26 (Box 4)
  - Honor Code - Fundamental Standard, special: 9/7/95 - 8/6/87; AD 3.10 (Box 4)
  - President's Office, 9/18/96 - 8/18/97; AD 4 (Box 4)
  - President's House/Staff/Car, 9/16/96 - 7/22/97; AD 4.7 (Box 4)
  - University Cabinet-Lowell Price, 9/5/96 - 8/18/97; AD 4.13 (Box 4)
  - Legal- University Counsel, special:10/16/95-8/29/97; AD 4.19 (Box 4)
  - General Correspondence, special 9/15/95-8/23/97; AD 4.20 (Box 5)
  - News clippings, 34178; AD 4.20.1 (Box 5)
  - Condolence Letters, 9/4/96 - 8/18/97; AD 4.20.2 (Box 5)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 9/19/96 - 3/21/97; AD 4.20.3 (Box 5)
  - Appreciation Letters, 9/11/96 - 7/8/97; AD 4.20.4/1 (Box 5)
  - Invitations, 9/96 - 8/25/97; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 5)
  - Nonsense, 9/96 - 8/97; AD 4.20.5 (Box 5)
  - Recommendation (search) letters, 9/96 - 8/97; AD 4.20.6 (Box 5)
  - Recommendation Letters, students, 10/15/96 - 3/12/97; AD 4.20.6/1 (Box 5)
  - Complaint Letters, 10/1/96 - 4/30/97; AD 4.20.7 (Box 5)
  - Solicitations, general misc favor req., special 1/7/96-8/31/97; AD 4.20.8 (Box 5)
  - University Communications (administ), 9/96 - 8/97; AD 4.22 (Box 5)
  - Off.Campus Relations (formerly Ombudsman), spec.1/25/96-8/97; AD 6 (Box 5)
  - Admissions, special 7/15/96 - 8/28/97; AD 8.1 (Box 6)
  - Student Affairs, special 7/26/97-8/22/97; AD 8.8 (Box 6)
  - Cowell Student Health Center, 10/96 - 5/20/97; AD 8.9 (Box 6)
  - Stanford In Washington DC, 12/12/96 - 6/16/97; AD 8.10.1 (Box 6)
  - Overseas Studies Programs, 10/23/96 - 8/25/97; AD 8.11 (Box 6)
  - Financial Aid, 9/96 - 5/22/97; AD 8.12 (Box 6)
  - Housing Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, 9/11/96 - 8/4/97; AD 8.18 (Box 6)
  - Hanna Honeycomb House, special 10/9/96 - 5/3/97; AD 8.18.2 (Box 6)
  - Lake House, 6/25/97 only; AD 8.18.3 (Box 6)
  - Fraternities/Sororities-Greek Task Force not archived, 6/96-8/97; AD 8.18.8 (Box 6)
  - Housing/Dining Services-Student, 9/13/96-8/26/97; AD 8.18.11 (Box 6)
  - Residential Education, 10/96 - 6/97; AD 8.18.13 (Box 6)
  - Registrar - Bursar, 9/3/96 - 7/17/97; AD 8.21 (Box 6)
  - Black Affairs-file closed, special 2/21/97-10/27/97; AD 9.1 (Box 6)
  - Multicultural Development, special 12/95-5/8/97; AD 9.6 (Box 6)
  - Affirmative Action, Student, 10/2/96 - 6/9/97; AD 9.6.3 (Box 6)
  - Personnel Services/faculty-staff, 9/17/96 - 8/12/97; AD 10 (Box 6)
  - Employment Inquiries/requests, special 11/20/95-8/97; AD 10.1 (Box 6)
  - Outdoor Art Committee, 7/15/97 - 8/27/97; AD 10.7.4 (Box 6)
  - USE United Stanford Employees, 5/7/97 only; AD 10.7.8 (Box 6)
  - Student Grievance-incld Berkowitz '96, 3/12/97 - 7/16/97; AD 10.8.10/3 (Box 6)
  - Retirement, 9/11/96 - 6/22/97; AD 10.8.17 (Box 6)
  - Salaries, 9/26/96 - 8/15/97; AD 10.8.19 (Box 6)
  - Tuition Benefit Plan, 9/27/96-2/19/97; AD 10.8.22 (Box 6)
  - Operations/Maintenance, 9/16/96 & 10/3/96 only; AD 11.4 (Box 6)
  - Environmental Health and Safety, 9/96 - 12/96; AD 11.4.1 (Box 6)
  - Campus Security (old Nazi '95 stuff), 10/15/96-5/24/97; AD 11.6 (Box 6)
  - Stanford Events, 10/22/96-4/28/97; AD 11.7.5/1 (Box 6)
  - Lively Arts at Stanford, 10/25/96-4/25/97; AD 11.7.5/2 (Box 7)
  - Freshman Orientation, 9/13/96-9/20/97; AD 11.7.7 (Box 7)
  - Media, external, 9/25/96 - 8/29/97; AD 11.8 (Box 7)
  - Stanford University Press, 9/96-8/21/97; AD 11.8.9 (Box 7)
  - Surveys, questionaires, 10/1/96 - 8/25/97; Ad 11.8.10 (Box 7)
  - Media, internal, 9/10/96 - 8/21/97; AD 11.8.11 (Box 7)
  - VP for finance, 12/17/96 only; AD 12.2 (Box 7)
  - VP for Business and Finance, PAD 12.2/1, 10/3/96 only; AD 12.2/1 (Box 7)
  - VP for Finance, 10/9/96 - 2/7/97; AD 12.2/2 (Box 7)
  - Administrative Resources, 10/14/96 - 8/27/97; AD 12.2/3 (Box 7)
  - Stanford Management Co., 2/14/96 - 8/7/97; AD 12.3 (Box 7)
  - Internal Auditing, 10/96-8/7/97; AD 12.4 (Box 8)
  - Budget, 9/96 - 6/13/97; AD 12.5 (Box 8)
  - Tuition, 11/5/96 - 7/25/97; AD 12.5.4 (Box 8)
  - Conflict of Interest/consulting, 11/7&25/96-12/18/96; AD 12.7.1 (Box 8)
  - Insurance Risk Management, 95 doc + 6/20/96+10/4/96; AD 12.8 (Box 8)
  - Restricted Funds, 9/12/96 only; AD 12.9.1 (Box 8)
  - John Ford - Development stuff, 9/30/96 - 8/11/97; AD 12.10 (Box 8)
  - Development Office isc, 10/96 - 8/97; AD 12.10.1 (Box 8)
  - Foundations/Corps Misc., 9/3/96 - 8/28/97; AD 12.10.4 (Box 9)
  - CHAD United Way, use AD 4.20.8, 9/26/96 - 10.21/97; AD 12.10.8 (Box 9)
  - Tech/Licensing/Patents/Copyright, 9/23/1996 - 8/22/97; AD 12.11 (Box 9)
  - Land use, Buildings - catch all, 10/10/96 - 8/28/97; AD 12.14 (Box 9)
  - Art Gallery & Museums, 9/96 - 8/97; AD 12.14.7/1 (Box 9)
  - Museum - special - design competition, stuff for Cantor Museum; Ditto (Box 9)
  - Athletic Dept - use of space, 11/1/96 - 4/22/97; AD 12.14.7/2 (Box 9)
  - The Stanford Bookstore-end 8/97, 12/3/92 article of incorporp.; AD 12.14.7/5 (Box 9)
  - Facilities/Planning/Univ.Architect, 9/9/96 - 8/27/97; AD 12.14.7/29 (Box 9)
  - Faculty Club, 9/10/96 - 11/19/96; AD 12.14.7/30 (Box 9)
  - Jasper Ridge Biological Experimental, 9/4/96 - 8/29/97; AD 12.14.7/43 (Box 9)
  - Memorial Church, 9/23/96 - 8/1/97; AD 12.14.7/50 (Box 9)
  - Tresidder Memorial Union TMU, 9/27/96 only; AD 12.14.7/64 (Box 9)
  - White Plaza, 11/14/96 - 5/14/97; AD 12.14.7/67 (Box 9)
  - Accounting, 10/25/1996 - 1/97; AD 12.15 (Box 9)
  - Conferences, 9/4/96 - 7/22/97; AD 13.10.1 (Box 9)
  - Industrial Relations, 10/3/96 - 8/18/97; AD 15 (Box 9)
  - Alumni Relations, 10/31/96 - 5/5/97; AL 1 (Box 9)
  - Letters to Parents, 9/6/96 - 11/4/96; AL 1.1 (Box 9)
  - Alumni Corresp general, 9/96 - 8/97; AL 1.3 (Box 9)
  - Alumni Letter Siege (s), class notes issue of '96; AL 1.3.1 (Box 9)
  - Annual Graduate Summer letter, 9/96 - 8/97; AL 1.4 (Box 9)
  - Alumni Events, 10/13/96 - 8/97; AL 1.7 (Box 9)
  - Class Reunions, 10/11/96 only; AL 1.8 (Box 10)
  - Alumni Association, 9/96 - 7/97; AL 3 (Box 10)
  - SAA 2000 Stanford Alumni Assoc., 9/96 - 8/97; AL 3.1 (Box 10)
  - Bowman Alumni, 8/18/96-6/11/97; AL 4 (Box 10)
  - Alumni Giving, 1/24/97 - 7/14/97; AL 5 (Box 10)
  - Misc. Board of Trustee stuff, 9/96 - 8/97; B 1 (Box 10)
  - BoT General Correspondence -- Note:, final report of the Task Force; B 2 (Box 10)
  - BoT appointment nominating committee, 9/96 - 6/20/97; B 12 (Box 10)
  - BoT Agendas and pre-agendas, 9/25/95 - 4/10/97 special; B 13.3 (Box 10)
  - BoT Misc. Committee's, 9/26/96 - 6/16/97; B 14 (Box 10)
  - Trustee Committee on Finance & Admin, PB14.4 only 1/10/97; B 14.4 (Box 10)
  - BoT Land & Building Planning committee, 10/10/96 - 5/22/97; B 14.6 (Box 10)
  - Bot on Minority Alum Relations, 9/96-1/21/97 Note: this; B 14.11 (Box 10)
  - Academic Council, 11/7/96 & 8/15/97 only; C 1 (Box 10)
  - Academic Council - Senate, 9/16/96 - 8/5/97; C 2 (Box 10)
  - Academic Council Advisory Board, 9/96 - 8/8/97; C 3 (Box 11)
  - Academic Council Steering Committee, 1/28/97 only; C 4.1 (Box 11)
  - Comm on Academic Appraisal/achieve., PC 5.1 - 10/23/96 ONLY; C 5.1 (Box 11)
  - Rhodes Marshall Scholarships, 12/3/96-12/17/96 only; C 5.1.4 (Box 11)
  - Comm on Tech in Teach and Learning, 9/16/96-8/14/97; C 5.7.2 (Box 11)
  - Misc University Committees, 10/29/96-7/31/97; C 6 (Box 11)
  - Committee of Fifteen, 10/15/96-4/28/97; C 6.1 (Box 11)
  - Government Relations, Office of, 9/12/96-8/31/97; G 1 (Box 11)
  - CA State Govn't - all agencies, 9/96 - 8/19/97; G 1.2 (Box 11)
  - Environmental Protection Agency, 1/31/97 & 2/5/97 only; G 2.3 (Box 11)
  - U. S. Government Relations, 9/96 - 8/22/97; G 3 (Box 11)
  - Department of Defense, 11/19/96-8/7/97; G 3.7 (Box 11)
  - Department of Energy, 1/22/97-8/6/97; G 3.7.2 (Box 11)
  - NASA Nat'l Aeron. and Space Admin., 9/12/96 - 7/15/97; G 3.7.4 (Box 11)
  - NIH Nat'l Institutes of Health, 11/4/96-6/10/97; G 3.8.2 (Box 11)
  - USDE U. S. Dept. of Education, 9/96 -8/22/97; G 3.8.3 (Box 11)
  - NSF National Science Foundation, 9/13/96-8/27/97; G 3.19 (Box 11)
  - Federal Agencies, Misc., 9/27/96-2/20/97; G 3.29 (Box 11)
  - Local Government/local businesses, 9/11/96-8/25/97; G 4 (Box 11)
  - Foreign Government Relations Misc, 12/10/968/29/97; G 5 (Box 11)
  - CA Institute for Federal Policy Resch., 10/24/96-8/21/97; G 7 (Box 11)
  - Stanford in Government, 11/23/96-7/3/97; PG 8 (Box 11)
  - U. S. Supreme Court, 12/10/96-4/9/97; G 9 (Box 11)
  - Council Foreign Rel Int'l Policy, 10/14/96-8/97; G 10 (Box 11)
  - United Nations, 9/10/96-1/28/97; G 12 (Box 11)
  - School of Medicine Misc, 9/10/96-8/25/97; M 1 (Box 12)
  - Misc Medical School Departments, 9/10/96-8/6/97; M 5 (Box 12)
  - Faculty Medical Practices, 2/19/97 & 4/15/97 only; M 6 (Box 12)
  - VP for Medical Affairs, 9/1/96-12/2/96; SHS 5 (med) (Box 12)
  - Outside Organizations Misc, 9/13/96 - 8/27/97; O 1 (Box 12)
  - Council on Competitiveness, 7/24/96 - 8/28/97; O 1.2 (Box 12)
  - SRI Stanford Research Institute, 12/9/96 - 7/17/97; O 2.11 (Box 12)
  - Outside Educational Groups, 12/3/96 - 8/25/97; O 3 (Box 12)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Edu, 9/16/96 - 4/30/97; O 3.1 (Box 12)
  - CA Academy of Science, 6/18/96 - 8/21/97; O 3.2 (Box 12)
  - Consortium of Social Sciences, 5/19/97 - x's 2; O 3.3 (Box 12)
  - Amer Acad Arts and Sciences, 9/4/96-8/29/97; O 3.7 (Box 12)
  - ACE Amer Countion of Education, 8/21/96-8/27/97; O 3.8 (Box 12)
  - NAICU Nat'l Assoc Independ. Coll/Univ, 9/9/96-8/28/97; O 3.10 (Box 12)
  - Amer Council of Learned Societies, 9/11/96 - 2/21/97; O 3.12 (Box 12)
  - College Entrance Exam Board, 9/5/96-8/20/97; O 3.25 (Box 12)
  - Aspen Institute, 9/13/96-8/12/97; O 3.37 (Box 12)
  - Institute of International Education IIE, 12/2/96-8/29/97; O 3.38 (Box 12)
  - Monterey Institute of Int'lStudies, 2/26/97 only; O 3.39 (Box 12)
  - NAS NAT'L ACAD. SCIENCES, 9/3/96-8/21/97; O 3.43 (Box 12)
  - Nat'l Acad. of Engineering, 9/24/96-5/13/97; O 3.43.1 (Box 12)
  - NCAA Nat'l Collegiate Athletic Assoc, 9/5/96-8/11/97; O 3.44 (Box 12)
  - Pac 10 - actual corresp. kept, O 3.47 (Box 13)
  - CA Business & Higher Ed Forum, 9/96-8/97:; O 3.56 (Box 13)
  - AAHE Amer Assoc Higher Ed, 9/13/96 - 6/15/97; O 3.57 (Box 13)
  - Athletic Organizations Misc, 12/5/96-2/15/97; O 4 (Box 13)
  - Medical Organizations Misc, 11/15/96 - 2/11/97; O 5 (Box 13)
  - Political Groups Misc, 9/27/96-7/9/97; O 6 (Box 13)
  - Research Organizations Misc, 10/28/96 - 6/24/97; O 7 (Box 13)
  - Rand Institute for Civil Justice, 11/11/96-2/14/97; O 7.9 (Box 13)
  - NRC National Research Council, 12/20/96-6/11/97; O 7.11 (Box 13)
  - Council of Presidents, Univs Resch Assoc, 10/11/96-7/31/97; O 7.16 (Box 13)
  - Other Colleges/Universities-selectively, 9/96 - 8/97; O 8 (Box 13)
  - AAU Assoc.Amer.Univ's 9/96-8/97, filed selectively:; O 8.7 (3 files) (Box 13)
  - Assoc of Governing Boards of Univ/Coll, 10/22/96-8/5/97; O 8.8 (Box 13)
  - AICCU Assoc Independent CA Coll/univ, 9/12/96-8/29/97; O 8.9 (Box 14)
  - Caltech, 11/14/96-11/27/96; O 8.16 (Box 14)
  - CA State Universities, 11/20/96-8/15/97; O 8.17 (Box 14)
  - Columbia University, 11/27/96-8/18/97; O 8.18 (Box 14)
  - Cornell University, 1/24/97 only; O 8.19 (Box 14)
  - Harvard University, 5/23/96-8/8/97; O 8.23 (Box 14)
  - Peking University (see Beida program), 8/18/96-7/31/97; O 8.30 (Box 14)
  - Princeton University, 10/28/96-6/10/97; O 8.36 (Box 14)
  - Nine Provosts, 10/8/96 & 5/6/97 only; O 8.39 (Box 14)
  - Univ of CA - all campuses, 9/19/96-8/31/97; O 8.43 (Box 14)
  - University of Chicago, 10/10/96-8/29/97; O 8.44 (Box 14)
  - University of Michigan, 10/25/96-8/6/97; O 8.45 (Box 14)
  - Brigham Young University, 3/26/96-3/30/96; O 8.46 (Box 14)
  - University of Oregon, 9/18/96-7/29/97; O 8.47 (Box 14)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 12/4/96-2/3/97; O 8.48 (Box 14)
  - USC Univ Southern CA, 9/5/96-6/23/97; O 8.49 (Box 14)
  - University of Washington, 2/10/97 only; O 8.50 (Box 14)
  - WASC West. Assoc. Sch's/Colleges, 7/1/91-8/13/97 special; O 8.52 (Box 14)
  - Yale University, 2/13/97-7/21/97; O 8.53 (Box 14)
  - Western College Association, 10/4/96-4/3/97; O 8.54 (Box 14)
  - Inaugurations - other schools, 8/30/96-7/31/97; O 8.55 (Box 14)
  - Bay Area Economic Forum, 9/3/96-8/22/97; O 11 (Box 14)
  - CA Council on Sci/Technology, 12/18/96-8/5/97; O 12 (Box 14)
  - American Philosophical Society, 9/1/96-8/20/97; O 15 (Box 14)
  - Research Misc, 10/18/96-1/6/99; R 0 (Box 14)